Garrett Rumschik

Columbus, Ohio, United States

rumschik.2@gmail.com

9374165998

linkedin.com/in/garrett-rumschik

Summary

Full-stack developer with over 6 years of experience developing back-end data structures for web applications, maintaining and deploying API's, and supporting front-end/mobile developers. Additional experience in utilizing various Cloud Services including AWS, GCP, and Azure. Ohio State University Graduate and Columbus resident.

Experience



Full-stack Software Developer

Novacoast

Oct 2023 - Present (7 months)

- Enterprise Engineer Consultant in charge of leading entire enterprise security divisions with adoption, integration, and maintenance of Cloud-Native Application Protection Platform.
- Work with Security teams utilizing various Public cloud platforms to integrate their stacks with our platform.
- Experience deploying and maintaining kubernetes clusters to integrate with different services, as well as maintaining jobs and load balancing.
- Work closely with clients to create custom Automation solutions with a variety of languages that would handle interfacing their platform with ours.



Full Stack Developer

MindForge LLC

Dec 2018 - May 2023 (4 years 6 months)

- Develop and maintain web application to facilitate the management and communication of construction companies
- Develop and maintain RESTAPIs using Python for integration with desktop client and mobile applications
- Was part of a small team on a 2 year effort to overhaul the backend data structures of the entire application, as well as leading the charge on creating a newly designed v2 API.
- Help maintain automated deployment using CI/CD pipelines including comprehensive testing
- Worked to implement caching to reduce improve efficiency.
- Experience with deployment of new features to production environments utilizing various AWS Cloud Services.



IT Specialist

Abercrombie & Fitch Co.

Aug 2018 - Dec 2018 (5 months)

- Performed administration and access support for a number of internal/proprietary systems and applications
- Implement and expand Identity & Access Management tool sets to their full potential

- Provided inter-departmental collaboration by escalating unresolved issues to appropriate support functions.
- Established service by walking callers through new installations and configurations.
- Performed quality assurance check of tickets processed by team

Education

The Ohio State University

Bachelor's degree, New Media & Technology 2013 - 2018 Bachelor of Arts in New Media and Technology Minor in Computer Information Science

Selected Coursework: Discrete Structures, Advanced C++, Software Design (Java), Advance UNIX, User-Centered Web Design, Data Structures (Java), Computer Interface and Human Fidelity, Principles of Human-Computer Interaction, Communication Technology, Communication Research Methods, Video Games and the Individual, Social Media,

Skills

Python • AWS • RESTful API • MySQL • Linux • Docker Products • Data Access Object (DAO) • Server Administration • Databases • CI/CD